

Javier Borbolla Ureña

Fullstack developer

Contact



636 78 80 93



jebx.dev



javierbuinfo@gmail.com

Idioms

Spanish - Native English - Conversational (B2)

Languages

Js Javascript 4 years Node|S 4 years F HTML5 4 years CSS3 4 years React 2 years Python 2 years C# 2 years **Bash** 2 years Ts Typescript +1 year Redux +1 year MongoDB +1 year Solidity +1 year PHP +1 year MySQL +1 year Angular -1 year R R -1 year **G** (++ -1 year Assembly -1 year

> +16 technologies, libraries and frameworks that could be interested in my website

> > https://jebx.dev

About me

Self-taught programmer for 6 years. Passionate about learning new techniques and languages. Whenever I can, I try to optimize and automate all the processes that are in my hand. My hobby is programming everything I can think of.

I have a high capacity for analysis and problem solving.

Education

Certificated in deep learning & CUDA 2021-2021 - University of Malaga

Expert in reverse engine and malware intelligence 2021-2021 - University of Malaga

Cybersecurity master 2020-2021 - Valencian International University

Web Application Development 2017-2019 - High School Severo Ochoa

Microcomputer systems and networks 2015-2017 - High School Severo Ochoa

Professional Experience

Software developer

2018 - Present

4 years of personal and autonomous development. Knowledge in more than 35 technologies, languages and frameworks. Good practices, use of interfaces, classes, enums, etc.. Knowledge in **git, jira**, **SOLID principles, hexagonal architecture**. Habituated to do **sprints** and follow the **Scrum** process. Fullstack develop with **MERN stack** tendency. Passionate about find bugs and optimize everything. I have do the entire develop of +10 websites and writed a lot of scripts and bots. Facility with **requests manage**, **sessions**, **JSONs**, **sockets**, **async functions and multithreading**. I have analyzed malware and i know obfuscation techniques

Frontend developer and bug fixer

2022 - 2022, NTT DATA - Jazztel

Develop and maintenance of the Jazztel's Website with **Angular and NodeJS.** Diary and weekly coordinance with some teams and direct interlocution with the client. Diary use of **Jenkins, Jira and Git.** In addition, i was mandated to find and solve bugs in the testing servers.

Frontend developer

2020 - 2020, MBVR

I was head of frontend development for a startup related to security against Covid-19. Development started with **C# and Blazor** but we ended up migrating to **C# and React (Redux + SemanticUI)**. Weekly meetings with the back team. I was also in charge of adding security to the network and to the intraconnections (**JWT**, **encryption**, **etc.**).

RPA software developer

2019 - 2019, Accenture - Movistar

Development and improvement of Movistar's internal software. Use of **Blueprism** to automate the processes carried out by the customer service team and in stores. I improved some of these softwares by performing **web scrapping** with the use of **HTTP requests** and thus optimizing the execution speed x5.